http://www.hifivesports.com/privacy_policy/

Effective March 14th, 2017
Welcome to Hifivesportsclubs.com.
We understand that you are concerned about how your personal information is collected and used.
Please be assured that we take privacy very seriously and are committed to safeguarding personal information.
This notice describes our Privacy Policy and covers the personal information that we collect through our websites, hifivesportsclubs.com and hifivefranchising.com (the “Sites”).
This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that may be collected by the Company offline or through other means.
By visiting our Sites, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Types of Personal Information Collected.
We collect and maintain personal information provided to us by individuals who register with our Sites or who otherwise send us personal information.
Such information may include a user’s name, business or home address, phone number, e-mail address, or other information that a user may give us.
We also collect personal information passively through the use of cookies and other technology.
A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server.
Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and serve the primary purpose of providing convenience features that will save you time.
We use cookies to track your log-in status, and the pages of the Sites that you have visited.
If you are logged-in to the Sites, we use cookies to track the time of your last log-in and the contents of your shopping cart.
You have the option to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer.
We also gather information concerning the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address of individuals that visit our Sites.
An IP address provides general statistical information, and other basic information that we use for system administration such as debugging.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information.
We use the Personal Information that you disclose to us to allow you to use the features on the Sites, perform the services that you request of us, respond to your inquiries, analyze trends and statistics, update the Sites and support our customer relationship with you. If you request to be put on our promotional mailing list, we will use the information that you give us to send you announcements and other materials from time to time.
Each e-mail you receive from us will give you the option to unsubscribe.
You can also request to be removed from our mailing list at any time by sending an email to info@hifivesports.com.
We do not sell or lease personally identifiable information to third parties.
We only share such information with third parties who provide services to the Company, including Google Analytics, to the extent necessary to provide you with services or information that you request of us or to analyze trends and statistics relating to our Sites.
These partners do not have any right to use your personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us.
We reserve the right to provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain Site-related services (such as web hosting or maintenance services) on our behalf.
We may disclose information that we maintain when required to do so by law or where reasonably necessary to protect our rights or a third party’s rights, for example, in response to a court order, a subpoena, a request by a law enforcement agency or to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of any third party.
We also reserve the right to disclose the information to any third party to prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our Sites and to protect the rights, property and safety of the Company, users of our Sites and the public.
Do Not Track (DNT).
We do not track our users over time and across third party websites and, therefore, our Sites do not respond to DNT signals.
Children’s Privacy.
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act imposes certain requirements on websites directed at children under 13 that collect information from those children, and on websites that knowingly collect information from children under 13.
Our Sites are not directed at children under 13 and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.
If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 13 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us without your consent, please contact us at info@hifivesports.com so that we may delete the minor’s information.
If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.
Protection of Personal Information.
We make reasonable efforts to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any personal information you choose to give us.
We have security technology and procedures in place to ensure that all information stored on our database is secured against unauthorized access and use. Although we will strive to take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Inadvertent disclosures may occur.
Security of Personal Information on Other Websites.
Our Sites may contain links to websites operated by third parties that are not under our control or supervision.
We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites. These websites may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policies at all.
We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other websites to see how your personal information will be handled before providing them with your personal information. Changes to the Personal Information We Have Collected.
Registered Users of our Sites can access, review, and edit their registration information on our Sites by emailing us at
info@hifivesports.com. If you would like us to delete your registration information, you can email us at the same email address.
Please be aware, however, that even after your request for deletion is processed, we may, for a time, retain residual information about you in backup and/or archival copies of our database.
Applicable Law.
The laws of the State of California will govern this Privacy Policy without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.
Effective Date and Modifications.
This policy is effective as of March 14th, 2017.
Please note that we may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, at our sole discretion, by posting the modified policy on our Sites.
The modifications will be effective upon posting, unless some other date is specified.
You should review this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications.
Your use of any of our Sites constitutes your full acceptance of the Privacy Policy in its then-current form.
Questions or Comments.
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at info@hifivesports.com..
© 2020 Hi-Five Sports Franchising LLC. All Rights Reserved.
